interactiveticketing.com 2011-10-04

# Privacy Policy

INTERACTIVE TICKETING PRIVACY POLICY

INTERACTIVE TICKETING respects the privacy of its users, and has developed this policy to communicate our commitment to your privacy. We encourage you to read this information carefully before using our services, and we encourage you to contact us if you have any questions or concerns.

What Personal Information is Collected?  
When you purchase tickets from our website, we use your personally identifiable information in strictly limited ways. This information is necessary to complete your transaction, and for us to assist you directly if you need help.  This information is collected only when you fill out the forms on our web site.  We also collect your IP address and internet provider information for security purposes.

Do we share the information?  
The information you provide when purchasing tickets is provided to the producer of the event for which you purchase tickets, so that the producer may periodically email you or contact you with regard to their events.  We do not provide your personal information to any other third party vendors.

INTERACTIVE TICKETING does not utilize any of your information for any purpose other than:  (1) to complete your transaction; or (2) to assist you if you need help with the transaction. 

What Are Cookies and how are they used?  
Cookies are pieces of information that a web site sends to your computer while you are using the web site. When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate your access to our web site. 

What about third party advertisers?  
INTERACTIVE TICKETING does not use third party advertisements on its web sites, and does not interact or work with third party advertisers. 

What type of security do we use?  
We use Secured Socket Layer (“SSL”) security, which encrypts all information that you submit to our web site.  In addition, we do not store credit card numbers on our servers; and we work on an ongoing basis to maintain PCI compliance.

Conditions of Use  
In addition to providing data to the producer of the event for which you purchase tickets on our web site, we reserve the right to release account and other personal information that we believe is appropriate to comply with the law, or to protect the rights, safety or property of INTERACTIVE TICKETING and its clients. This includes exchanging information with fraud protection agencies, and law enforcement officials.
